

I am a software developer with a background in healthcare administration, and experience in web development from my training through the Nology course.

I have loved all things technology from childhood, and have always dreamt of a career in the industry. I have been tinkering with computers and software dating back to my first computer, and even in the healthcare sector I enjoyed challenging myself with writing scripts or programs to automate our workflow.

I am driven by a logical and analytical mindset, and always find unique solutions to problems. I am confident in my ability to communicate with stakeholders and understand their needs. Outside of work, I enjoy teaching myself a variety of skills such as 3D modelling and PC building.

### **PROJECTS**



#### **E-Commerce**

A React based web application of a mock online shopping platform, that uses a Firestore database as backend.



### To Do List

A full stack application of a to-do list, with a frontend in Typescript using React, and a backend in Java using Spring Boot.



#### **Book Search**

A React based web application that uses the Google Books API to lookup books.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Hills Health Solutions | 2022 - 2023

I worked as an Administration Coordinator for the Nurse Call Service Team. I served as the first point of contact for the company, where I managed service and sales orders from our customers. I also managed various administrative tasks, such as scheduling and invoicing.

### \_nology | 2024 - CURRENT

I worked as part of a small team completing tickets for the backend of a student metrics application. The app tracks student performance, assessment results, and project feedback. We worked in MySQL, Typescript & NestJS to create a logging strategy for seeder classes, diagnosed and resolved errors in the migration script, and created a reporting domain with CRUD endpoints.

# **KEY SKILLS**

Git
HTML
CSS/SASS
Javascript &
Typescript

React Java Spring SQL/MySQL NestJS

# **EDUCATION**

Victorian Certificate of Education
Werribee Secondary College | 2019 - 2020

Full Stack Engineer Program \_nology | 2024